<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service xmlns="http://github.com/dret/sedola">
    <title>Activity Streams 2.0</title>
    <documentation source="http://www.w3.org/TR/activitystreams-core/">This specification details a model for representing potential and completed activities using the JSON format.</documentation>
    <mediatype def="application/activity+json">
        <documentation source="http://www.w3.org/TR/2014/activitystreams-core/#introduction">In the most basic sense, an "activity" is a semantic description of a potential or completed action. In the former case, the activity expresses what can or might be done with a particular object, while in the latter case, it expresses what has already been done. It is the goal of this specification to provide a JSON-based syntax that is sufficient to express metadata about activities in a rich, human-friendly, machine-processable and extensible manner. This may include constructing natural-language descriptions or visual representations about the activity, associating actionable information with various types of objects, communicating or recording activity logs, or delegation of potential actions to other applications.</documentation>
        <document xml:id="as-activity">
            <title>Activity</title>
            <documentation source="http://www.w3.org/TR/activitystreams-core/#activities">Activity objects are specializations of the base Object type that provide information about ongoing or completed actions.</documentation>
        </document>
        <document xml:id="as-collection">
            <title>Collection</title>
            <documentation source="http://www.w3.org/TR/activitystreams-core/#collection"> Collection objects are a specialization of the base Object that contain a listing of other Objects. The Collection object is used primarily as the root of an Activity Streams Document, but can also be used as the value of object properties. Collections have both a logical model and a physical serialization. While the logical view of a collection might contain a large number of objects, any single serialized representation might include only a subset of those objects, with specific "paging" Links used to reference additional serialized representations that include additional subsets. Such representations are known as "multi-page collections", with each serialized subset representing a single "page".</documentation>
        </document>
    </mediatype>
</service>