<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service primary="IETF" secondary="RFC" id="6768">
    <title>Media Resource Control Protocol Version 2 (MRCPv2)</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc5829">The Media Resource Control Protocol Version 2 (MRCPv2) allows client hosts to control media service resources such as speech synthesizers, recognizers, verifiers, and identifiers residing in servers on the network. MRCPv2 is not a "stand-alone" protocol -- it relies on other protocols, such as the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP), to coordinate MRCPv2 clients and servers and manage sessions between them, and the Session Description Protocol (SDP) to describe, discover, and exchange capabilities. It also depends on SIP and SDP to establish the media sessions and associated parameters between the media source or sink and the media server. Once this is done, the MRCPv2 exchange operates over the control session established above, allowing the client to control the media processing resources on the speech resource server.</documentation>
    <uri-scheme def="session">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6787#section-13.6">The URI is intended to identify a data resource previously given to the network computing resource. The purpose of this scheme is to permit access to the specific resource for the lifetime of the session with the entity storing the resource.</documentation>
    </uri-scheme>
    <media-type def="application/nlsml+xml">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6787#section-6.3.1">The Natural Language Semantics Markup Language (NLSML) is an XML data structure with elements and attributes designed to carry result information from recognizer (including enrollment) and verifier resources.</documentation>
    </media-type>
    <media-type def="text/grammar-ref-list">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc6787#section-9.9">The body of the RECOGNIZE method of the MRCP protocol may contain a list of grammar URIs specified in content of media type 'text/grammar-ref-list'. This type defines a list of grammar URIs and allows each grammar URI to be assigned a weight in the list.</documentation>
    </media-type>
</service>