<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Badly written spec which nowhere simply defines the headers in a simple and summarized way. Gave up searching eventually and concluded that Section 2.5 may be the best way to get at least a bit of an overview of what the header fields are used for. -->
<service primary="IETF" secondary="RFC" id="7469">
    <title>Public Key Pinning Extension for HTTP</title>
    <documentation source="https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc7469">This document defines a new HTTP header that allows web host operators to instruct user agents to remember ("pin") the hosts' cryptographic identities over a period of time. During that time, user agents (UAs) will require that the host presents a certificate chain including at least one Subject Public Key Info structure whose fingerprint matches one of the pinned fingerprints for that host. By effectively reducing the number of trusted authorities who can authenticate the domain during the lifetime of the pin, pinning may reduce the incidence of man-in-the-middle attacks due to compromised Certification Authorities.</documentation>
    <http-header def="Public-Key-Pins">
        <documentation source="https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc7469#section-2.5">Whenever a UA receives a Valid Pinning Header, it MUST set its Pinning Metadata to the exact Pins, Effective Expiration Date (computed from max-age), and (if any) report-uri given in the most recently received Valid Pinning Header.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Public-Key-Pins-Report-Only">
        <documentation source="https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc7469#section-2.5">Upon receipt of a Public-Key-Pins-Report-Only response header field, the UA should evaluate the policy expressed in the field, and SHOULD generate and send a report. However, failure to validate the Pins in the field MUST have no effect on the validity or non-validity of the policy expressed in the PKP field or in previously noted Pins for the Known Pinned Host.</documentation>
    </http-header>
</service>