<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service primary="IETF" secondary="RFC" id="8631">
    <title>Link Relation Types for Web Services</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc8631">Many resources provided on the Web are part of sets of resources that are provided in a context that is managed by one particular service provider. Often, these sets of resources are referred to as "Web services" or "Web APIs". This specification defines link relations that represent relationships from Web services or APIs to resources that provide documentation, descriptions, metadata, or status information for these resources. Documentation is primarily intended for human consumers, whereas descriptions are primarily intended for automated consumers. Metadata provides information about a service's context. This specification also defines a link relation to identify status resources that are used to represent information about service status.</documentation>
    <link-relation def="service-doc">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc8631#section-4.1">The "service-doc" link relation type is used to represent the fact that a resource or a set of resources are documented at a specific URI. It identifies service documentation for the context that is primarily intended for human consumption.</documentation>
    </link-relation>
    <link-relation def="service-desc">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc8631#section-4.2">The "service-desc" link relation type is used to represent the fact that a resource or a set of resources are described at a specific URI. It identifies service description for the context that is primarily intended for consumption by machines. Often, it is provided in a format that is consumed by tools, code libraries, or similar components.</documentation>
    </link-relation>
    <link-relation def="service-meta">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc8631#section-4.3">The "service-meta" link relation type is used to link to available metadata for the service context of a resource. It identifies general metadata for the context that is primarily intended for consumption by machines. In many cases, it is provided in a representation that is consumed by tools, code libraries, or similar components.</documentation>
    </link-relation>
    <link-relation def="status">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc8631#section-5">Identifies a resource that represents the context's status. Such a link may not be available from all resources provided by a Web service, but from select resources such as a service's home resource.</documentation>
    </link-relation>
</service>