<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This description ignores all the HTTP header fields that have been specified in the newer RFC 2616 (which was obsoleted as well). -->
<service xmlns="http://github.com/dret/sedola">
    <title short="HTTP/1.1">Hypertext Transfer Protocol - HTTP/1.1</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc2068">The Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) is an application-level protocol for distributed, collaborative, hypermedia information systems. It is a generic, stateless, object-oriented protocol which can be used for many tasks, such as name servers and distributed object management systems, through extension of its request methods. A feature of HTTP is the typing and negotiation of data representation, allowing systems to be built independently of the data being transferred. HTTP has been in use by the World-Wide Web global information initiative since 1990. This specification defines the protocol referred to as "HTTP/1.1".</documentation>
    <http-header def="Content-Version">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc2068#section-19.6.2.2">The Content-Version entity-header field defines the version tag associated with a rendition of an evolving entity. Together with the Derived-From field, it allows a group of people to work simultaneously on the creation of a work as an iterative process. The field should be used to allow evolution of a particular work along a single path rather than derived works or renditions in different representations.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="URI">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc2068#section-19.6.2.5">The URI header field has, in past versions of this specification, been used as a combination of the existing Location, Content-Location, and Vary header fields as well as the future Alternates field. Its primary purpose has been to include a list of additional URIs for the resource, including names and mirror locations. However, it has become clear that the combination of many different functions within this single field has been a barrier to consistently and correctly implementing any of those functions. Furthermore, we believe that the identification of names and mirror locations would be better performed via the Link header field. The URI header field is therefore deprecated in favor of those other fields.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Public">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc2068#section-14.35">The Public response-header field lists the set of methods supported by the server. The purpose of this field is strictly to inform the recipient of the capabilities of the server regarding unusual methods. The methods listed may or may not be applicable to the Request-URI; the Allow header field MAY be used to indicate methods allowed for a particular URI.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Content-Base">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc2068#section-14.11">The Content-Base entity-header field may be used to specify the base URI for resolving relative URLs within the entity. This header field is described as Base in RFC 1808, which is expected to be revised.</documentation>
    </http-header>
</service>