<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../core/sedola.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <title>Delta encoding in HTTP</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc3229">This document describes how delta encoding can be supported as a compatible extension to HTTP/1.1. Many HTTP (Hypertext Transport Protocol) requests cause the retrieval of slightly modified instances of resources for which the client already has a cache entry. Research has shown that such modifying updates are frequent, and that the modifications are typically much smaller than the actual entity. In such cases, HTTP would make more efficient use of network bandwidth if it could transfer a minimal description of the changes, rather than the entire new instance of the resource. This is called "delta encoding."</documentation>
    <http-header def="Delta-Base">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc3229#section-10.5.1">The Delta-Base entity-header field is used in a delta-encoded response to specify the entity tag of the base instance. A Delta-Base header field MUST be included in a response with an IM header that includes a delta-coding, if the request included more than one entity tag in its If-None-Match header field. Any response with an IM header that includes a delta-coding MAY include a Delta-Base header.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="IM">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc3229#section-10.5.2">The IM response-header field is used to indicate the instance-manipulations, if any, that have been applied to the instance represented by the response. Typical instance manipulations include delta encoding and compression.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="A-IM">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc3229#section-10.5.3">The A-IM request-header field is similar to Accept, but restricts the instance-manipulations that are acceptable in the response. A response may be the result of applying multiple instance-manipulations. When an A-IM request-header field includes one or more delta-coding values, the request MUST contain an If-None-Match header field, listing one or more entity tags from prior responses for the request-URI.</documentation>
    </http-header>
</service>