<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../core/sedola.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <title>Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WebDAV) Ordered Collections Protocol</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc3648">This specification extends the Web Distributed Authoring and Versioning (WebDAV) Protocol to support the server-side ordering of collection members.  Of particular interest are orderings that are not based on property values, and so cannot be achieved using a search protocol's ordering option and cannot be maintained automatically by the server.  Protocol elements are defined to let clients specify the position in the ordering of each collection member, as well as the semantics governing the ordering.</documentation>
    <http-header def="Ordering-Type">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc3648#section-5.1">When a collection is created, the client MAY request that it be ordered and specify the semantics of the ordering by using the new Ordering-Type header with a MKCOL request. For collections that are ordered, the client SHOULD identify the semantics of the ordering with a URI in the Ordering-Type header, although the client MAY simply set the header value to DAV:custom to indicate that the collection is ordered but the semantics of the ordering are not being advertised.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Position">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc3648#section-6.1">When a new member is added to a collection with a client-maintained ordering (for example, with PUT, COPY, or MKCOL), its position in the ordering can be set with the new Position header.  The Position header allows the client to specify that an internal member URI should be first in the collection's ordering, last in the collection's ordering, immediately before some other internal member URI in the collection's ordering, or immediately after some other internal member URI in the collection's ordering.</documentation>
    </http-header>
</service>