<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../core/sedola.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <title>Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP/1.1): Range Requests</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc7233">The Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) is an application-level protocol for distributed, collaborative, hypertext information systems. This document defines range requests and the rules for constructing and combining responses to those requests.</documentation>
    <http-header def="Accept-Ranges">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc7233#section-2.3">The "Accept-Ranges" header field allows a server to indicate that it supports range requests for the target resource.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Range">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc7233#section-3.1">The "Range" header field on a GET request modifies the method semantics to request transfer of only one or more subranges of the selected representation data, rather than the entire selected representation data.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="If-Range">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc7233#section-3.2">If a client has a partial copy of a representation and wishes to have an up-to-date copy of the entire representation, it could use the Range header field with a conditional GET (using either or both of If-Unmodified-Since and If-Match.)  However, if the precondition fails because the representation has been modified, the client would then have to make a second request to obtain the entire current representation. The "If-Range" header field allows a client to "short-circuit" the second request. Informally, its meaning is: if the representation is unchanged, send me the part(s) that I am requesting in Range; otherwise, send me the entire representation.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Content-Range">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc7233#section-4.2">The "Content-Range" header field is sent in a single part 206 (Partial Content) response to indicate the partial range of the selected representation enclosed as the message payload, sent in each part of a multipart 206 response to indicate the range enclosed within each body part, and sent in 416 (Range Not Satisfiable) responses to provide information about the selected representation.</documentation>
    </http-header>
</service>