<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service id="urn:ietf:id:snell-more-link-relations" xmlns="http://github.com/dret/sedola">
    <title>Additional Link Relations and the urn:social Namespace</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations">This specification defines a number of additional Link Relation Types that can used for a variety of purposes.</documentation>
    <link def="to">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to a resource that is considered to be part of the public primary audience of the link's context.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="bto">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to a resource that is considered to be part of the private primary audience of the link's context.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="cc">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to a resource that is considered to be  part of the public secondary audience of the link's context.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="bcc">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to a resource that is considered to be part of the private secondary audience of the link's context.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="from">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to a resource that is publicly considered to be the originator of the link's context.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="bfrom">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to a resource that is privately considered to be the originator of the link's context.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="source">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to the original source of information contained by the context resource.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="provider">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to the resource that provided the context resource. Typically, this would be used to identify the entity publishing the resource.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="generator">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to the resource that generated the context  resource. Typically, this would be used to identify the software application that created the context resource.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="mentionedby">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">Refers to a resource that mentions the context resource in some fashion. This, for example, would be used when an article mentions another article, or a social status update mentions a particular user, etc.</documentation>
    </link>
    <link def="location">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-snell-more-link-relations#section-3">References a URI/IRI that represents a physical or logical location with which the context resource is associated.</documentation>
    </link>
</service>