<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service primary="IETF" secondary="I-D" id="wilde-linkset">
    <title>Linkset: Media Types and a Link Relation Type for Link Sets</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-wilde-linkset">This specification defines two media types and a link relation type for sets of links. The media types can be used to represents links in a standalone fashion, in one case in the native format used in the HTTP Link header, and in the other case in a JSON-based format. The link relation can be used to reference these kind of standalone link sets, so that a resource can indicate that additional links putting it into context are available someplace else. One typical scenario is when the number of links to put in  an HTTP Link header field becomes too big, and thus these links should be provided by a distinct resource.</documentation>
    <link-relation def="linkset">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-wilde-linkset#section-4">The "linkset" link relation type is used by a resource to link to a resource that provides a set of links. Typically the Context IRI of these links  is the URI of the responding resource but links with other Context IRIs MAY be provided.</documentation>
    </link-relation>
    <media-type def="application/linkset">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-wilde-linkset#section-5.1">This document format is identical to the payload of the HTTP Link header. It is defined in Section 3 of RFC 5988bis, more specifically by its ABNF production rule for "Link" and subsequent ones.</documentation>
    </media-type>
    <media-type def="application/linkset+json">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-wilde-linkset#section-5.2">For applications that prefer a JSON serialization of link set resources, the following definition provides a JSON serialization which is intended to faithfully reproduce the abstract model of RFC 5988bis.</documentation>
    </media-type>
</service>