<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<service xmlns="http://github.com/dret/sedola">
    <title>Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP/1.1): Caching</title>
    <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-ietf-httpbis-p6-cache">The Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) is an application-level protocol for distributed, collaborative, hypertext information systems. This document defines requirements on HTTP caches and the associated header fields that control cache behavior or indicate cacheable response messages.</documentation>
    <http-header def="Age">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-ietf-httpbis-p6-cache#section-5.1">The "Age" header field conveys the sender's estimate of the amount of time since the response was generated or successfully validated at the origin server.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Cache-Control">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-ietf-httpbis-p6-cache#section-5.2">The "Cache-Control" header field is used to specify directives for caches along the request/response chain. Such cache directives are unidirectional in that the presence of a directive in a request does not imply that the same directive is to be given in the response.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Expires">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-ietf-httpbis-p6-cache#section-5.3">The "Expires" header field gives the date/time after which the response is considered stale. The presence of an Expires field does not imply that the original resource will change or cease to exist at, before, or after that time.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Pragma">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-ietf-httpbis-p6-cache#section-5.4">The "Pragma" header field allows backwards compatibility with HTTP/1.0 caches, so that clients can specify a "no-cache" request that they will understand (as Cache-Control was not defined until HTTP/1.1). When the Cache-Control header field is also present and understood in a request, Pragma is ignored.</documentation>
    </http-header>
    <http-header def="Warning">
        <documentation source="http://tools.ietf.org/html/draft-ietf-httpbis-p6-cache#section-5.5">The "Warning" header field is used to carry additional information about the status or transformation of a message that might not be reflected in the status code. This information is typically used to warn about possible incorrectness introduced by caching operations or transformations applied to the payload of the message.</documentation>
    </http-header>
</service>